clubrsx.com 2002-02-04

# Club RSX | Corporate | Privacy Policy

Club RSX Privacy Policy  

ClubRSX.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: ClubRSX.com.

**Browsing**  
We collect certain information when you visit ClubRSX.com to improve the quality of your experience. The information that we collect depends upon where you travel within our site. Anytime that you visit our site to browse, or to read or download information, we collect and store the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to areas of our site, and to help us make our site more useful and interesting to our visitors. We use "cookies" on our site to enable you to save your Auto ID information and to expedite any future orders. A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online "shopping cart" to keep track of items you wish to purchase. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site's computer, which, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. Most consumers do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit websites. If you want to know when this happens, or to prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a website attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer. Our site relies upon the use of cookies to enhance your shopping experience, but our cookies do not contain nor track your personally identifiable information.

**Online Registration Request**  
If you choose to provide more information to us through our online registration, you may provide your e-mail address and create a password or provide greater detail, such as your name, address, postal address and telephone number ("Registration Information"). Your Registration Information will enable us to provide you information regarding future products and services that may suit your particular interests. You may access and modify or remove your Registration Information by selecting the "Your Account" button in our online store. If you remove your Registration Information, we will not use it in any way.

**Product Purchases**  
If you choose to purchase a product from us, we will collect your personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, billing postal address, shipping postal address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date ("Purchase Information") in order to properly process your purchase. You may not modify or remove your Purchase Information - even if you cancel or return your product order - as it is necessary to maintain a record of your initial product purchase.

**Do We Share Your Information?**  
We will share your Registration Information with third party independent contractors who will help us provide you ClubRSX.com product offers via e-mail and/or regular mail, who are bound not to share or use our data. Your Purchase information will also be sent to third party vehicle component merchants in order to fulfill the product that you ordered; however, these parties are contractually bound not to share your Purchase Information with anyone.  
We may sell or exchange your Registration Information or Purchase Information to third parties who want to market products to you; or resell your Registration Information to those companies who do.  
We may provide certain information in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process or in the event that we find that your actions on our site violate any laws, our terms of use, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This site contains links to other sites. It is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All credit card information utilizes state-of-the-art Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology and SET compliant.
